[Waco] Sanger-Heights Neighborhood Term Paper and Research collection, Inclusive: 1986-1995, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
[Waco] Sanger-Heights Neighborhood Term Paper and Research collection
Inclusive: 1986-1995, undated
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
2925
Robb, Allan P.
16 document boxes 6 OVZ boxes (cassettes)
The [Waco] Sanger Heights Neighborhood Term Paper and Research collection tells the history of the Waco neighborhood through written and oral materials collected by Dr. Allan Robb during his English 1304 course taught at Baylor University. Items include term papers, oral interviews, tax records, floor plans, photographs, maps, and copies of other historical documents.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Dr. Allan P. Robb was a lecturer in the English Department at Baylor University from 1982-1996. One of the courses he taught was English 1304: Thinking Writing, and Research, one of two courses accepted to fulfill the advanced writing requirement in the core curriculum of the Arts and Sciences degree. The course was “designed to teach students to gather and evaluate information from a variety of sources and to incorporate ideas from these sources into writing of a research paper.”
From 1986-1995, Robb used the class to research and document the history of the Sanger Heights Neighborhood in Waco, Texas. Students acquired oral interviews, tax records, floor plans, photographs, maps, and copies of other historical documents and utilized their findings to write term papers for the English 1304 course.
Scope and Content
The Properties series includes term papers and original research conducted for the class. Items such as photographs, hand drawn floor plans, tax records, and other historical information about houses and homeowners of specific properties are present. The Cassettes series includes oral history interviews of property owners and tenants of listed locations.
Arrangement
Written materials and audiocassettes were previously intermixed in folders and arranged by street address, numerical streets first, followed by alpha streets. Materials have been separated into two series, I: Properties, and II: Cassettes while maintaining the original order. In addition, a continuous numbering system (ex. 1 of 3, 2 of 3, etc.) extends across the series to signify that materials for individual properties are present in both series.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 2925. Acquired 1986-00-00
Related Resources
Related references
Baylor Bulletin. Vol. 96. Issue No. 1. May 1993. Accessed 2021 April 27.
BU Records: Retired Professors and Administrators Program, Accession #BU/312, Box # 22, Folder # 6, The Texas Collection, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Places
Sanger Heights Neighborhood (Waco, Tex.); Waco (Tex.) -- Buildings, structures, etc.
Subjects
Dwellings -- Research -- Texas -- Waco.; Dwellings -- Texas -- Waco -- History.; Historic buildings -- Research -- Texas -- Waco.; Historic buildings -- Texas -- Waco.; Neighborhoods -- Texas -- Waco.
Genres
Audiocassettes.; Floor plans.; Photographs.; Tax records.; Term papers.
- Properties, 1985-1996, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  The Properties series, dated 1986-1995, includes term papers documenting the history of residences and businesses in the Sanger Heights Neighborhood of Waco, Texas. Research items present include photographs, hand drawn floor plans, copies of tax records, and other historical documents that provide insight into ownership and upkeep of individual addresses. In addition, names of the students who created the files are included. The series is arranged by street address and in good condition.
  Index Terms
  Genres
  Photographic print
  - 811 N. 4th Street, Ray V. Sardessai (1 of 2), 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1316 N. 5th Street, Wendi Frindell, 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1412 N. 6th Street, Justin Carswell, 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 812 N. 9th Street, Jennifer O’Brien, 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1302 N. 13th Street, Anastasia Nenadyshina (1 of 2), 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1302 N. 13th Street, Anastasia Nenadyshina (2 of 2), 1994 December (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 708 N. 15th Street, Peter Rebane, 1991 May (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 514 N. 16th Street, Karen Caldbeck (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 605 N. 16th Street, Dawn Christopherson, 1992 December (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 623 N. 16th Street, Keri Berg, 1990 December (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 624 N. 16th Street, Pamela F. Reynolds (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 702 N. 16th Street, Jennifer Booker, 1992 May (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 709 N. 16th Street, Sally Ann Geis, 1990 December (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 726 N. 16th Street, Kira Kuzmiak, 1987 April (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 726 N. 16th Street, Katherine D. Lilly (1 of 2), 1989 December (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 920 N. 16th Street, Tanya Owen (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 927 N. 17th Street, Melanie M. Sohocki, 1990 December (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1015 N.17th Street, Angela C. Lengefeld, 1989 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 521 N. 18th Street, Evan Hunter (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - 910 N. 18th Street, Wendi R. Parker (1 of 3), 1990 December (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 910 N. 18th Street, Wendi R. Parker (2 of 3), 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1105 N. 18th Street, Kenneth R. Bates (1 of 2), 1989 December (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1109 N. 18th Street, Christy Prather, 1992 May (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1220 N. 18th Street, Kelli Phillips, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1226 N. 18th Street, Joannah Evans (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 624 N, 19th Street, Chas. Kipp, 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 707 N. 19th Street, Nathan Bac, 1989 December (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 920 N. 19th Street, Rhonda S. Hefner, 1985 April (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 934 N. 19th Street, Tracey Goodwin (1 of 4), 1989 April (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 724 N. 20th Street, Hannah Black, 1990 December (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 908 N. 21st Street, Jena Gardner, 1990 April (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 506 N. 22nd Street, Charles J. Glick, 1989 December (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 511 N. 22nd Street, William Walker Edgar (1 of 3), 1988 December (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 511 N. 22nd Street, William Walker Edgar (2 of 3), 1988 December (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 515 N. 22nd Street, Don W. Sapaugh, 1987 April (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 521 N. 22nd Street, Jessamyn Allen (1 of 4), 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 521 N. 22nd Street, Jessamyn Allen (2 of 4), 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 521 N. 22nd Street, Jessamyn Allen (3 of 4), 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 524 N. 22nd Street, Jeff Laidlaw, 1985 April (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 612 N. 22nd Street, Jennifer Ann Mori, 1987 December (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 912 N. 22nd Street, Lesley O’Connell (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 912 N. 22nd Street, Clare Satterfield (1 of 3), 1989 April (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 912 N. 22nd Street Clare Satterfield (3 of 3), 1989 April (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 925 N. 22nd Street, Caroline Percy (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1020 N. 22nd Street, Scott Fligor (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1020 N. 22nd, Jeff Jones, 1990 May (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1312 N. 22nd Street, Kristen Mills, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1312 N. 22nd Street, Stephanie Sagebiel (1 of 2), 1990 April (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - 1312 N. 22nd Street, Shovi L. Parvin (1 of 2), 1987 April (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - 1312 N. 22nd Street L. Parvin (2 of 2), 1987 April (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 523 N. 23rd Street, Lori Rankin (1 of 3), 1988 December (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 523 N. 23rd Street, Lori Rankin (2 of 3), 1988 December (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 915 N. 23rd Street, Cathy Stamey (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 928 N. 23rd Street, Kurt Keller (1 of 2), 1988 April (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 800 N. 25th Street, Scott Bradley Delaney, 1990 December (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 118 N. 30th Street, Pamela A. Fierbach (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 526 N. 30th Street, Sheila D. Shapka (1 of 2), 1995 May (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 526 N. 30th Street, Sheila D. Shapka (2 of 2), 1995 May (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 1304 S. 3rd Street, Christina Zachgo, May 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 1310 S. 3rd Street, Block 68, Parcel 9, Lydia Lopez, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - S. 3rd Street, Block 68, Lot 6, 1324, 1324a, 1326, 1326a, 1328, 1328a, Allison Lamb, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - S. 3rd Street, Block 68, Lot 7, 1324, 1324 ½, 1326, 1326 ½, Eric Deuillet, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1328 & 1328 ½ S. 3rd Street, Susan Bell (1 of 2), 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1330 S. 3rd Street, Leslie L. Bowers, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1331 & 1329 S. 3rd Street, Nicole Reynolds, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1339 S. 3rd Street, Raul Ortega, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1400 S. 3rd Street, Janet Dromgoole, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1415, 1415 ½, 1417, 1417 ½ S. 3rd Street, John J. Rodriguez, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1423 & 1425 S. 3rd Street, Chris May, 1994 July (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 1904 Algonquin Ave, Scott Phillips, 1990 December (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 2010 Algonquin Ave, Christine Var Konda, 1990 December (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 1906 Austin Ave, Kendra Kubiak (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 2424 Austin Ave, Richard Helmer, 1991 May (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 2600 Austin Ave, Amy E. Baker (1 of 2), 1992 November (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 2600 Austin Ave, Amy E. Baker (2 of 2), 1992 November (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 3315 Austin Ave, Clay Pulliam (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 3315 Austin Ave, Clay Pulliam (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Bagby Addition, Robyn Martin, 1987 July (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Bell Addition, John D. King, 1987 July (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Belmont Addition, Rick Chaney, 1987 July (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1801 Bosque Blvd., Ericka H. Hazard, 1985 April (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1919 Bosque Blvd., Brett L. Bowden (1 of 4), 1988 December (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1919 Bosque Blvd., Brett L. Bowden (2 of 4), 1988 December (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 2128 Bosque Blvd., Soren Bjorn, 1990 December (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2129 Bosque Blvd., (1 of 2), 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 2200 — 2208 Bosque Blvd., Stan Granberry, 1990 December (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 2201 Bosque Blvd., Sonja Dimitrijevich (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 2300 Bosque Blvd, Paige Reid (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 3503 Carondolet, Jim Kordoban, 1995 December (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 2413 Columbus Ave, LynnLi Beach, 1992 May (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 3311 Castle Ave, Tommy E. Brian, 1995 December (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 3317 Castle Ave, Ernesto Carmona, 1995 December (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 3624 Castle Ave, Jennise E. Walker, 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 3625 Castle Ave, Cassie Garner, 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 3626 Castle Ave, Matt Clark (1 of 2), 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 3725 Castle Ave, Kristian Zamber, 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sanger Heights Neighborhood Inventory (1 of 2), 1986 June (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Sanger Heights Neighborhood Inventory (2 of 2), 1986 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 3411 Chateau Ave, Caroline Kohl (1 of 2), 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 3501 Chateau Ave, Nikki Wisely (1 of 2), 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 3525 Chateau Ave, Misty Redfield (1 of 2), 1995 December (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1811 Colcord Ave, David Phelps, 1990 December (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1805 Colcord Ave, Monica Martinez, 1981 November (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1900 Colcord Ave, Paige K. Bardo (1 of 4), 1990 May (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1901 Colcord Ave, John Durham, 1987 December (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1901 Colcord Ave, Lucy Parks (1 of 4), 1992 December (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 2033 Colcord Ave, Lynn E. Fowler, 1990 December (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 2101 Colcord Ave, Jimmy Everett, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 2105 Concord Ave, Carl Kirk Smith, 1988 December (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 2122 Colcord Ave, Theresa Pumilia, 1987 April (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 2125 Colcord Ave, Fabiola Fernandez, 1989 December (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 2128 Colcord Ave, Beth McCleary (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 2128 Colcord Ave, Beth McCleary (2 of 2), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 2128 Colcord Ave, Chris Withrow & Beth McCleary (1 of 3), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 2200 Colcord Ave, Chrisanna Simpson (1 of 4), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 2200 Colcord Ave, Chrisanna Simpson (2 of 4), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 2201 Colcord Ave, Lori Evans (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 2211 Colcord Ave, Susie Kopper, 1986 April (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 2223 Colcord Ave, Kraig Milton (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 2224 Colcord Ave, David Eldridge, 1990 May (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 2301 Colcord Ave, Dawn R. Huse, 1992 May (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 2309 Colcord Ave, Aristidis Pontikas (1 of 2), 1992 April (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 2309 Colcord Ave, Aristidis Pontikas (2 of 2), 1992 April (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 2315 Colcord Ave, Angela Richey (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 2316 Colcord Ave, Nathan Urban, 1986 December (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 2316 Colcord Ave, Erin L. O’Brien (1 of 2), 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - 2316 Colcord Ave, Chris Nunnalee (1 of 2), 1989 December (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 2316 Colcord Ave, Chris Nunnalee (2 of 2), 1989 December (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 2420 Colcord Ave, Pamelyn Allen, 1988 April (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - 2615 Colcord Ave, Sarah Jones (1 of 2), 1989 April (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 3000 Colcord Ave, Jill Smith, 1992 May (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 3028 Colcord Ave, Kirk Hatcher, 1992 May (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - 2402 Colcord Ave, Greg Simmons, 1985 April (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - 2402 Colcord Ave, Wayne Wilder, 1992 December (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 2407 & 2425 Colcord Ave, Laura Howell, 1987 May (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 2412 Colcord Ave, J. Caraway, 1987 April (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 2412 Colcord Ave, Tom Whitt (1 of 4), 1986 December (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 2412 Colcord Ave, Tom Whitt (2 of 4), 1986 December (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 2412 Colcord Ave, Tom Whitt (3 of 4), 1986 December (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 2425 Colcord Ave, Carol Garris, 1992 May (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 2518 Colcord Ave, Michael T. Kahley, 1990 December (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 2523 Colcord Ave, Sofia Aguilera, 1989 December (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 1815 Colonial Ave, Carrie A. Platt (1 of 2), 1992 May (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 1820 Colonial Ave, Shauna Claiborne, 1990 December (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 1825 Colonial Ave, Mary Thompson (1 of 3), 1992 December (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - 2201 Colonial Ave, Stephanie Fox, 1987 April (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - 2207 Colonial Ave, Jefferey Stewart, 1990 December (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - 2224 Colonial Ave, Brad Schwall, 1988 April (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - 2224 Colonial Ave, Laura Marie Walter, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - 2224 Colonial Ave, Joshua Phillips, 1990 April (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 2301 Colonial Ave, Amy Beckwith (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 2304 Colonial Ave, Stephanie Murphee, 1988 December (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - 2317 Colonial Ave, John Duarte, 1989 December (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 2324 Colonial Ave, Lisa Burris, 1992 December (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 617 Columbus Ave, Cristin Hardin, 1990 December (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 617 Columbus Ave, Tonya James, 1992 April (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Dean’s Addition, Beth Cathey, 1987 July (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - 1901 Ethel Ave, Lisa Rugeley, 1988 April (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2015 Ethel Ave, Steve Graves (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 2015 Ethel Ave, Ludianna Thomas, 1990 December (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 2211 Ethel Ave, David Brady, 1987 December (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - 2211 Ethel Ave, Hao V. Vuong (1 of 2), 1987 April (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - 2219 Ethel Ave, Jim Beavers, 1987 April (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 2223 — 2225 Ethel Ave, Alexander Chan (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - 2309 Ethel Ave, Robert Raborn, 1989 December (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2316 Ethel Ave, Lana Elliott, 1987 April (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 2317 Ethel Ave, Michelle Isaac, 1990 December (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - 2403 Ethel Ave, Shannon L. Potts (1 of 5), 1990 May (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - 2417 Ethel Ave, Laura Simpson, 1986 April (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 2505 Ethel Ave, Eric Hein, 1988 December (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - 2105 Fort Ave, Brant Newsom, 1988 April (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 2127 Fort Ave, Darnell Reese, 1990 December (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 2901 Fort Ave, Reagan Hughes (1 of 2), 1994 December (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - 2200 Gorman Ave, Anne Marie Oliver, 1988 August (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 2208 Gorman Ave, Christopher Renberg, 1987 December (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - 2314 Gorman Ave, Michael Stevens (1 of 2), 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 2316 Gorman Ave, Sandra L. Keyes (1 of 2), 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 2220 Gorman Ave, Joseph J. Pothanikat (1 of 3), 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 2220 Gorman Ave, Joseph J. Pothanikat (2 of 3), 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 2226 Gorman Ave, Sharon Stacha (1 of 2), 1986 December (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 2300 Gorman Ave, Jamie Augustine, 1986 April (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 2301 Gorman Ave, Brent Schultheis (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 2315 Gorman Ave, Jeff Williams, 1986 April (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2316 Gorman Ave, Holly Faulhaber (1 of 3), 1986 December (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 2316 Gorman Ave, Holly Faulhaber (2 of 3), 1986 December (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 3818 Herwol Ave, Mindi Hardison (1 of 2), 1995 December (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 3825 Herwol Ave, Courtney MacNaught (1 of 2), 1995 December (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Highland Place Addition, Kathryn Wells, 1987 July (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 2121 Homan Ave, Cheli Smith (1 of 2), 1989 December (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 2121 Homan Ave, Rachel E. Wolfe (1 of 2), 1987 December (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 2300 Homan Ave, Lisa Miller, 1990 December (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 2401 Homan Ave, Mark E. Pittman, 1987 April (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 2401 Homan Ave, Julie Harris, 1992 December (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 2411 Homan Ave, Timothy Weeks (1 of 3), 1988 December (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 2411 Homan Ave, Timothy Weeks (2 of 3), 1988 December (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 2926 Homan Ave, Timothy R. Hutson (1 of 2), 1985 April (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2926 Homan Ave, Timothy R. Hutson (2 of 2), 1985 April (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Huaco Heights, Linda S. Guillen, 1987 July (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - 1525 Morrow Ave, Mildred G. Walker (1 of 2), 1989 Spring (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - 1525 Morrow Ave, Mildred G. Walker (2 of 2), 1989 Spring (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - 1525 Morrow Ave, Mark Dayala, 1984 December (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - 1605 Morrow Ave, Melanie Long, 1990 December (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 1625 Morrow Ave, Kristin Wilkinson, 1987 April (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - 1625 Morrow Ave, Kristen Malacarne (1 of 3), 1992 December (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - 1625 Morrow Ave, Kristen Malacarne (2 of 3), 1992 December (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - 1625 Morrow Ave Millie Nelson (1 of 2), 1990 May (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Chay B. Ung (1 of 6), 1992 December (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Chay B. Ung (2 of 6), 1992 December (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 1700 Morrow Ave, Chay B. Ung (3 of 6), 1992 December (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - 1700 Morrow Avenue, Christopher T. Forsythe (1 of 5), 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1700 Morrow Avenue, Christopher T. Forsythe (2 of 5), 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - 1710 Morrow Ave, Andi Ramon, 1990 December (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - 1712 Morrow Ave, Chris Reynolds (1 of 2), 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - 1801 Morrow Ave, Melissa Reeves (1 of 2), 1986 April (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - 1801 Morrow Ave, Lise C. De Lisle, 1987 April (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1815 Morrow Ave, John Anderson (1 of 2), 1987 April (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - 1815 Morrow Ave, John Anderson (2 of 2), 1987 April (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 1815 Morrow Ave, Verena Albrand (1 of 2), 1990 December (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - 1816 Morrow Ave, Tim Murphy, 1986 December (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 1819 Morrow Ave, JoRhea Nagel (1 of 2), 1990 December (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - 2009 Morrow Ave, Melinda Morris, 1987 April (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - 2020 Morrow Ave, Jennifer Maples, 1992 December (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 2110 Morrow Ave, Ha Nguyen, 1988 December (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - 2116 Morrow Ave, Lori Ann Lindsay (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - 2130 Morrow Ave, Dennis A. Boomhower, 1990 December (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - 2200 Morrow Ave, Tracy Allen, 1987 April (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - 2215 Morrow Ave, Kristin Banks, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - 2225 Morrow Ave, Andrea J. Weis (1 of 3), 1986 December (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - 2225 Morrow Ave, Andrea J. Weis (2 of 3), 1986 December (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - 2305 Morrow Ave, Stephanie Mounger, 1987 April (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - 2425 Morrow Ave, Nga Tran, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - 2820 Morrow Ave, Todd Rexrode (1 of 2), 1990 May (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - 3300 Morrow Ave, Shannon Dixon (1 of 2), 1990 May (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2020 Parrott Ave, Erin McBride, 1992 May (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - 2111 Parrott Ave, Aimee Michelle Mahoney, 1992 December (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 2200 Parrott Ave, Susan Rebecca Harvey (1 of 3), 1988 May (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - 2301 Parrott Ave, Jay Karlson, 1986 April (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 2315 Parrott Ave, Molly Woods, 1992 December (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 2315 Parrott Ave, David Dodd Williams, 1987 April (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 2320 Parrott Ave, Christopher Bart Barber (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2325 Parrott Ave, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 2326 Parrott Ave, Rhonda Crouch (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 2326 Parrott Ave, Monica D. Lopez, 1988 April (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 2420 Parrott Ave, Sheryl Stewart (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - 2422 Parrott Ave, Carlos Ortiz (1 of 2), 1988 December (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - 2422 Parrott Ave, Carlos Ortiz (2 of 2), 1988 December (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - 2515 Parrott Ave, Misti Cutsinger, 1988 November (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - 2518 Parrott Ave, Michael Jakowitsch (1 of 2), 1992 December (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - 1703 Sanger Ave, Debbie Nystrom, 1985 April (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - 1721 Sanger Ave, John Donovan, 1987 December (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - 1815 Sanger Ave, Conrad B. Quintyn, 1988 April (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - 1914 Sanger Ave, Ji Young Kim (1 of 3), 1992 December (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - 1914 Sanger Ave, Ji Young Kim (2 of 3), 1992 December (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - 1914 Sanger Ave, Michelle Stephenson, 1990 December (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - 1915 Sanger Ave, Shawn R. Stepp (1 of 2), 1988 November (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - 2225 Sanger Ave, Andrea M. Booth, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 2228 Sanger Ave, Wayne Wilder, 1990 December (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - 2709 Sanger Ave, Jennifer Julia, 1995 April (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - 2709 Sanger Ave, Karen Kanwhen, 1995 March (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2715 Sanger Ave, Matt Rowan (1 of 2), 1994 December (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - 2726 Sanger Ave, Marcie Sharadin, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)